thesisterproject.com 2017-08-07

# privacy policy - A Way To Garden

YOUR PRIVACY is important, and we want you to understand what information is collected when you visit http://awaytogarden.com or http://awaytogarden.com/book (the websites) and how we use it.

**Information You Provide**

You do not need to register to use or access the websites.  However, the sites may make comment sections, forums, message boards, or similar features available to its users. You may be required to register for these features, particularly if you wish to leave comments or post information. When you prepare a comment, you may have the opportunity to add the name of your website or blog within the submission form; if you do, your name as it appears in the published comment will be hotlinked to your blog or website. Should you choose to e-mail us, we will have your e-mail address and whatever other personally identifiable information you send us.

If you do register and provide us with personally identifiable information in the process, we will use it as is described below.  Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not share your information with any third-party organization without your express consent.

Please note that if you post comments or other information to the main blog or any forum or message board, any personally identifiable information you provide may be read, collated and used by anyone viewing them.  As such, we are not responsible for personally identifiable information you may choose to make available through these features.

Visitors to our websites have the opportunity to sign up to receive communications from us, including our e-mail newsletters.  We rely on a third party e-mail marketing company ([http://constantcontact.com](http://constantcontact.com/)) to deliver this service.  If you would like to sign up, you will need to provide your email address. These communications may include our regular newsletter, product promotions, and any other information that we feel you might find interesting. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications by emailing us at awaytogarden (at) gmail (dot) com, by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link in any email we send to you, or by replying to any email we send you and entering the word UNSUBSCRIBE in the subject line.

**Log Files**

We employ commonly used third-party analytic services that automatically collect anonymous information about visits to our websites and store this information in server log files. This information does not identify individual users: it includes such data as IP addresses, browser types, referring pages, operating system used and date/time stamps.  We do not have direct control over the tools these third-party analytic services use to collect data. We use this information to get a better sense of how our websites are being used over time.

**Cookies**

Our site uses “cookies” to provide easier and faster access to website features such as log-ins or repeat visits.  Cookies are very small text files that are stored on personal computers for reference purposes. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you have submitted while on our site.

We may use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie makes it easier for you to explore our sites, but expires when your browser is closed.  A persistent cookie may stay on your hard drive for an extended period of time, and can perform such activities as storing your log-in information for forums or message boards so you do not have to sign in every time you visit those areas.  Persistent cookies may be used to enable us to track and target the interests of our users so as to enhance the visitor’s overall experience.

We use a third party to serve some of the ads on our websites.  We must alert you that it may use cookies, web beacons, or both to collect data in the ad-serving process:

  * Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to this website.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). (Users may, alternatively, opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative [opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).)
  * Cookies of other [third-party vendors or ad networks](https://www.google.com/adsense/support/bin/answer.py?answer=94149) may also be used to serve ads on this site: A list of these potential vendors, with links to their sites, [is located here](https://www.google.com/adsense/support/bin/answer.py?answer=94149). Users may visit those websites to opt out of cookies (if the vendor or ad network offers this capability). Users can opt out of some, but not all, of these cookies in one location at the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out website at [www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

[Click here for details from the Google Privacy Center.](http://www.google.com/privacy.html) We have no access to or control over any cookies or other devices that are used by any third-party advertisers or ad servers on our site.

**Links to Other Websites**

Our websites contain links to other sites that we do not control.  When you click on a link to another site, we urge you to read its privacy policy.  We are not responsible for the privacy practices or policies of any website other than our own.

**Access to Personally Identifiable Information**

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer wish us to possess your information, you may request correction, updating, or deletion of your information by emailing us at awaytogarden [at] gmail [dot] com.  Contact information is repeated at the end of this privacy policy.

**Security**

Our website is professionally maintained and we take reasonable steps to protect any information in our possession. Because no electronic storage system can ever be 100% secure, we do not guarantee the absolute security of your information.

**Legal Disclaimer**

We reserve the right to disclose personally identifiable information as required by law, if we believe disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or other legal process.

**Questions?**

If you have any questions or concerns, our contact information is as follows:

awaytogarden [at] gmail [dot] com

This privacy policy was last updated on March 15, 2013.
